好  该钱德了  好
Okay, Chandler. Okay.
你的星座运势显示
And your horoscope says:
"本月5日  某个特别的人会送你礼物"
"On the 5th, a special someone is going to give you a gift."
哇  那就先谢了
Oh, well, thank you in advance. Mm. Ha, ha.
"但会在12日  引发恋人间的口角"
"But the 12th brings a lover's spat."
你一定是拿我送的礼物开玩笑了
You're going to make a joke about my special present.
你为什么要这样啊
Why would you do that?
等等  "19日  暗恋你的人会向你表白"
Oh, wait and "On the 19th, a secret crush announces itself."
大家好  嘿
Hey, guys. Hey
天哪   是《麦克与吉事》的乔伊崔比亚尼
Oh, my God! It's Joey Tribbiani of Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
没错   今天才开拍
That's right. It's your first day.
你准备好要和机器人拍档   一起打击邪恶势力了吗
So are you psyched to fight fake crime with your robot sidekick?
还用问吗   在连续剧里担当主角
Am I psyched? The lead in my own TV series?
我都想好多年了
I've dreamed about this for years.
怎么可能没准备好
Why have I not been preparing?
不  乔伊  你这次一定技惊四座
No, Joey, you're gonna be great.
不过  菲比  我得跟机器人对戏   我对科技一窍不通
But I gotta act with a robot. Pheebs, I don't know anything about technology.
除了上色情网站外  我连用钱德的电脑都不会
I can't even use Chandler's computer, except to find porn.
那还是因为色情网站开机后是首页才找到的
And that's only because it's there when you turn it on.
我们的恋人口角  本月怕是会提前爆发啊
Our lover's spat will start a little early this month.
我等着
I'll be waiting.
老友记  第六季  第21集  拜见岳父
Friends  S06E21  The One Where Ross Meets Elizabeth's Dad
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
你是先看封面然后选书吗  真不该这样啊
Are you judging them by their covers? Because you're really not supposed to do that.
不是  我想选一本来用  我又要写新书了
No, I'm just deciding which one to use. I'm going to start writing another book.
因为上一本很畅销
Because the last one was such a big seller?
如果你好奇  告诉你吧  我已经写了14本书了
Well, if you must know, I have written 14 books.
因为读者只有我一个
And as I'm the only one who has read them...
我可以告诉你们  反响很热烈
...I can tell you that they have all been very well received.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你们等会儿有事吗
Hi. What are you doing later?
瑞秋和我要去剪头发
Oh, Rachel and I have to get our hair cut.
有吗  我想先知道他要干嘛
We do? I want to see what he wants first.
我刚得知伊丽莎白她爸想见我
I just found out Elizabeth's dad wants to meet me.
等等   电话别挂
Wait a minute. Hold the phone.
你难道不是伊丽莎白的爸爸吗
You're not Elizabeth's dad?
拜托啦   我真的想让她爸爸喜欢我
Come on, guys. I really want this guy to like me.
你们要是能留在这里  帮我说说好话
It would really help me out if you guys could be here...
将会帮我大忙   当然了  义不容辞
...to make me look good. Of course we'll help.
我们留在这里   谢了
We'll be here. Thanks.
我们都清楚家长会不好对付啊
We know how tough those parent-teacher conferences can be.
这是你的办公室场景
So here's your office set. Wow, huh?
麦克麦可维利   私家侦探
Mac Machiavelli, Private Investigator. Eh?
试穿一下演出服吧
Let's get you to wardrobe for a fitting. Okay.
嘿  我什么时候可以跟机器人见个面啊
Hey, uh, when do I get to meet the robot?
抱歉  那就现在吧  他也在这儿
I'm sorry, why don't we do that right now? He's right here.
好的  乔伊崔比亚尼   这位
Okay. Joey Tribbiani, this is--
哇  真是栩栩如生
Wow! He's so lifelike.
了不起
Unbelievable.
这位是韦恩   机器人"吉事"的发明者和操作者
This is Wayne, the man who created and operates C.H.E.E.S.E.
韦恩   你好
How do you do there, buddy?
你们两个慢慢聊   好的
I'll let you two guys get acquainted, huh? Okay.
刚才很抱歉
Sorry about that.
吉事呢  吉事就在这里
Uh, so where's C.H.E.E.S.E.? C.H.E.E.S.E. is right here.
麦克  幸会
Nice to meet you, Mac.
它是半成品吧  不是  怎么了
This is the temporary robot, right? No. Why?
我以为它会改造得更酷
Well, I just thought it was gonna be a really cool robot. y'know?
像魔鬼终结者  或者刚才的你
Like the Terminator, or, uh, when I first saw you.
我花了两年时间研发这个机器人   它非常先进
I spent two years developing this machine. It's absolutely state of the art.
抱歉  只是它看起来其貌不扬
I'm sorry. it just—I don't know it doesn't really look like it can do anything.
它能揍你
It can do this.
嘿  哇哦
Hey-Oh, ha, ha.
这是我爸  保罗史提芬斯  爸  这是罗斯盖勒
This is my father, Paul Stevens. Dad, this is Ross Geller.
保罗  幸会
It's great to meet you, Paul.
我比较喜欢伊丽莎白的男友  叫我史提芬斯先生
I prefer that Liz's boyfriends to address me as Mr. Stevens.
没问题  史提芬斯先生
Uh, Of course, of course. Mr. Stevens.
罗斯
Good. So, Ross...
你有什么毛病嘛
...what's your problem?
什么
Excuse me?
为什么不交年龄相近的女友
Why can't you get a girlfriend your own age?
这个  真好笑
Heh. It's funny...
这个  不好笑
Um, it's not funny.
我不喜欢你跟我女儿交往  罗斯
I don't like you going out with my daughter, Ross.
嗯  我看得出来
Okay, urn, I can see that.
但你要是给我机会  我一定能改变你的看法
But I think if you give me, urn, one chance, I can change your mind.
好啊   什么
Okay. What?
好  我给你机会改变我的看法
Okay. I'll give you one chance to change my mind.
计时1分钟
You've got one minute.
爸爸   好吧
Daddy. Fine.
2分钟   开始
Two minutes. Go.
l分50秒
A minute and 50 seconds.
好
Okay, um--
告诉你  我以前没做过这种事
I want you to know, I have never done anything like this before.
我是说  我跟别人交往过
I mean, I've been in, urn, relationships in general.
但没跟学生做过  不  我的意思
But I've never done it with a student. I mean, not...
不是那档子事   我们也没做过
Not "it." We haven't done "it."
当然我们做过一些事
Uh-We, I mean-I mean, we've done stuff...
好吧   笑话  讲个笑话轻松一下
Okay. Okay. A joke. A joke. Lighten the mood.
两个男人走进酒吧   一个是爱尔兰人
Um, two guys go into a bar. One of them is Irish.
我是爱尔兰人  结果爱尔兰人赢了
I'm Irish. And the Irish guy wins the joke.
罗斯  罗斯
Ross? Ross!
居然会在这里遇见你  天哪  谢天谢地
How crazy that we would run into you. Oh, my God! Thank you.
嗯
Um, uh--
史提芬斯先生  他们是我的朋友
Mr. Stevens, I'd like you to meet my friends.
菲比  摩妮卡和钱德
This is Phoebe, Monica, and Chandler.
你是伊丽莎白的父亲   难怪她有一种
So you're Elizabeth's father, huh? I can see now where she gets her...
粗犷的美
...rugged handsomeness.
你老婆可健在
Is there a Mrs. Stevens?
你老公还没死
There's a Mr. Bing!
不幸啊  丽莎出生后不久  她妈妈就过世了
No, unfortunately, Lizzie's mom passed away shortly after she was born.
我一手把她带大
I raised her by myself. Oh...
我常碰上这种反应
I get that a lot.
好  大家都坐吧
Okay, urn, why don't we all take a seat, you know? Heh.
我去帮大家叫些咖啡
And, uh, I'll get us all some, uh, coffees.
好  请诸位
Yeah, why don't you-Ahem. Uh...
畅所欲言
And you guys can talk about whatever you want.
想到什么就聊什么
Whatever pops into your head.
这时候在这里遇见罗斯  真怪啊
It is so strange seeing Ross here, this time of day...
通常他都要在儿童医院
...because usually he's at the children's hospital.
对   都没有约会
Yeah. But not looking for dates.
摩妮卡是罗斯的妹妹
So, um, Monica is Ross' sister.
他是个了不起的大哥
He's a great brother!
我也有个妹妹
I had a sister. Oh.
她过世了   哦
She passed away. Oh...
你们不用每次都表示同情
You don't have to do that every time.
不过  罗斯人真的很好  我们是大学室友
But, uh, Ross is a great guy. I was roommates with him in college.
相当的有趣
Funny story, heh, ha, ha...
你的大学室友一定死了  对吧
Your roommate in college died, didn't he?
他算是半死不活  对
A part of him did, yes.
来吧   保罗  伊丽莎白
Okay! Here we are, Paul, Elizabeth.
希望你们能找到愉快的话题
I hope you guys were finding something to talk about.
我们正在愉快   抱歉  我来晚了
Yes. We were just-Sorry I'm late.
不过我已经准备好了  帮你美言几句
But I am ready, ready to talk you up. Heh.
丽莎的爸爸什么时候来   我已经到了
When does Liz's father get here? I'm already here.
罗斯人最好了
Oh, Ross is so great.
甜心  你买了印着小女生的这种  不是说好买印着婴儿的那种吗
Honey, you got the kind with the little girl. You said we'd get the kind with the baby.
你说的那个婴儿的让你害怕   不  是小女生的才恐怖
You said the baby creeps you out. No, The little girl creeps me out.
你是说婴儿的  婴儿的为什么会让我害怕
You said the baby. Why would the baby creep me out?
那小女生有什么好怕的
Why would the little girl creep you out?
抱歉  你们讲慢点好吗
I'm sorry. Can you please talk a little slower.
你要写进书里  对  这是探讨两性关系的书
This is going in your book? Yeah, It's about relationships.
尔虞我诈  各种禁忌
You know, the traps, the pitfalls, what not to do.
接着说   太精彩了  什么
Keep going. This stuffs great. What?
再说一遍
Excuse me.
还有就是  真爱无敌
And how none of it matters when the people really love each other.
还有   人人都喜欢听好话
And how people will believe anything you tell them as long as it's a compliment.
喔   嗨   嗨
Oh, hi! Hi. Hi. Hi.
我的钥匙掉在这里什么地方了  那赶快找啊
I left my keys here somewhere. Oh, well, let's look for them.
在这里  嘿
Under here-Oh, hey!
嘿  是这串吗
Hey! Are these them?
不是
No.
好吧
All right. Oh.
是这串  太好了
Here they are. Good.
多谢帮忙   等等
Thanks for your help. Wait! Sorry!
保罗先生   叫我保罗就好
Mr. Paul? Just call me Paul.
保罗  我只是想说
Paul. Um, I just wanted you to know that...
罗斯人真的很好
...you know, Ross really is a great guy.
不如你跟他交往   省得我宰了他
Maybe you could date him then. it would save me the trouble of killing him.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你不像是个有20岁女儿的人
You just don't look old enough to have a 20-year-old daughter.
我们生她的时候很年轻
Well, we were very young when we had her.
我们  对啊   通常一男一女才能生孩子啊
Ah. We? Yeah, it usually takes two people to...
当然是  两个人才能生孩子  我知道
Oh, no! Yes! Of course. I know that.
我是问  现在是"我们"   还是只剩下你单身
What I meant was are you still "we" or are you just you?
只有我  单身
I'm just me. Yeah.
丽莎出生没多久   我老婆就死了
My wife died shortly after Lizzie was born.
喔
Oh.
你一手把她带大  对  没错
So you raised her all on your own? Yes, I did.
哦
Oh...
嘿   嘿
Hey. Hey.
第一天顺利吗   还不错
How was your first day? Great.
只是机器人有点闹别扭
Except I got a little attitude from the robot.
该死的机器人   它们本该是人类忠实的仆人
Damn those robots. They're supposed to be our faithful servants!
也不是机器人的问题   是操纵他的家伙
It wasn't the robot, it was the guy who controls him.
他不喜欢我   我正要去拿三明治
He doesn't like me. He had C.H.E.E.S.E. knock over the sandwich table...
他却操纵吉事  打翻了餐桌
...right when I was reaching for one. Ugh.
你为啥不解雇了他
Why don't you get him fired?
搞不好我会  我也不想这样  但我是个明星
I may have to. I hate to do it. But I'm the star, you know?
总不能老捡地上的三明治来吃吧
There's a limit to how many sandwiches I can eat off the floor.
抱歉
Excuse me.
乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
小子  总算找到你了  我帮你联系了一个试镜
Joe! I'm glad I found you! I got an audition for you.
哇   不过这事还没公开
Wow. The thing is, it's kind of on the q.t.
那个演员不知道   他可能会被换掉
The actor who has the part doesn't know he might be fired.
是一部连续剧的主角
It's the lead in a series.
麦克与吉事
Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
我就是《麦克与吉事》的主角
I'm the lead in Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
哦
Uh-oh.
乔伊
Joey?
嗨  罗斯
Hi, Ross.
我只想让他更喜欢你
I was just getting him to like you.
乔伊
Joey?
乔伊  嘿  罗斯
Joey! Hey, Ross.
罗斯  乔伊不在
Ross, Joey is not here.
那好   我就在这儿等等他
Okay, I'll just wait for him in here!
罗斯   没关系   你可以出来
Ross, it's okay. You can come out.
罗斯  没关系  是我啊
Yeah, Ross. It's okay. It's me...
史提芬斯先生
...Mr. Stevens.
哦  天哪   我刚才没看见你
Oh, I didn't... Oh, my gosh. I didn't even see you.
你肯定看见了  你走进来  表情古怪  然后就跑进了卧房
Sure you did. You came in, got all awkward and ran to the bedroom.
还一直喊   "乔伊  乔伊"
You were shouting, "Joey, Joey!"
再见  瑞秋  再见
Bye, Rachel. Bye.
我会再打给你  好  再见
I'll call you later. Okay. See you!
罗斯  再见
Bye, Ross. Ah, hoo. Ha, ha.
你在   你怎么了  你在怎么
What-what-what the—how da-how did-what the-how did-what?!
他的钥匙掉了  到处在找
Well, You know, he lost his keys. So he was looking for them.
在你的嘴里找
In your mouth?
不
No.
在楼下找  我们聊了2小时
Downstairs. And we got to talking...
我很喜欢他  就请他上来喝杯咖啡
...for two hours. I really liked him. I invited him for a cup of coffee.
你们就在咖啡厅里
You were at the coffee house!
罗斯  就算我亲了他  这有什么大不了的
Ross, what's the big deal? So I kissed the guy.
他是我女朋友的爸爸   这样子很怪
He's my girlfriend's father. Okay? It's weird!
你还跟我妹约会呢   那不一样
You dated my sister. That was different!
什么  有什么不一样  我觉得怪
What? Why? This is weird for me!
罗斯  听好  这样对你有好处
Ross, look. look this is good for you, okay?
承认吧  目前保罗一点也不喜欢你
Let's face it. So far the guy's not loving you.
但我可以改变他的看法   我有门路
But I can turn that around. I've got the inside track.
我们可以一起出去吃饭   我替你美言
We could all go out to dinner. y'know? And I could talk you up.
况且他是个超有名的律师
Plus the guy is a very, very successful lawyer.
很重要吗   绝对重要
How is that important? Oh, it's important.
很明显  能扮演麦克的人多如牛毛
Apparently, there's a million guys out there that can play Mac ...
机器人只有一个
...and there's only one robot.
能控制他的人更是独一无二   没想到他竟有生杀大权
And this one guy who controls it. I didn't know he could get me fired.
我该怎么办  乔伊
What am I gonna do? Well, Joey.
你是一个魅力男
You're a pretty charming guy.
谢了  但我现在面临困难
Thanks. But I have a problem to deal with.
宝贝  你得征服那个操作员
No, sweetie. You've got to win over the guy who controls C.H.E.E.S.E.
还得用力拍机器人的马屁
Go back there and kiss some serious robot ass!
好主意
That's not a bad idea!
既然明天要施展魅力  今天就不跟你们这伙人浪费了
If I have to turn on the charm tomorrow, I'm not wasting any of it on you guys.
不过菲比  我为你留了一点
Oh, actually I got a little bit saved for you, Pheebs.
你觉得  乔伊比我有魅力
So do you think, uh, Joey is more charming than me'?
对   不然我怎么会跟他睡觉
Yeah. That's why I'm sleeping with him on the side.
你想得美
Yeah, you wish.
"你想得美"   菲比  别再写我们了
"You wish." Phoebe, stop writing about us.
我没写你们   我写别人呢
I'm not writing about you. I'm writing about other people.
谁  摩莎和钱特
Who? Marsha and Chester.
好吧  写吧  我也要写菲莉丝的故事
Okay, fine. Fine. Then you know what? I will just write about Phyllis.
哼   嗯
Hmm. Huh.
"菲莉丝坐在椅子上"  我知道你想干嘛
"Phyllis is sitting in the chair." I see what you're doing.
"菲莉丝知道我想干嘛"
"Phyllis sees what I'm doing." Oh, ho.
哇  我终于自食恶果了
Ooh, I have tasted my own medicine and it is bitter.
早  嘿
Morning! Hey!
我最欣赏的天才和我的机器人搭档  好吗
How's my favorite genius and his robot buddy?
不许碰它  好  行了
Don't touch him! Okay. All right. Um...
韦恩  你老实说  我一直听说我会被换掉
Wayne, level with me. Okay? I keep hearing all these rumors that I might get fired.
他们还找人来试我这个角色
Okay, they even have actors coming in to read for my part.
拜托啦   再给我一次机会
Come on, man. You gotta give me a second chance.
我爱死这个小家伙了
I love this little guy-Aah.
好吧  难怪你从不让我碰他  拿去吧
Okay. That's why you didn't want me to touch him, right? There you go.
白痴  真是的
Stupid! I can't believe this! God.
嘿  你好吗
Hey, how are you doing?
看样子我是被放鸽子了
So it seemed that my prom date had stood me up.
罗斯还大方的提议要带我去
So Ross selflessly offered to take me.
好动听的故事啊
What a nice story. Heh.
罗斯上大学时
So Ross was in college...
想趁虚而入  就带一名少女参加高中舞会
...and decided to jump at the chance to take a young girl to her prom.
哇  我倒从没从这个角度想过这事
Wow. I definitely did not see that one backfiring.
我去下洗手间   你慢慢上
I'm gonna go to the bathroom. Yeah. Take your time.
其实我读大一   她高中毕业   所以倒也不是差很多
Just so you know, I was a freshman and she was a senior. So it wasn't as bad as--
罗斯  听着  我知道我一直在找你麻烦
Ross, look. I know I've been giving you a lot of jabs.
因为我爱女心切
It's partly because I'm very protective of Lizzie...
而且情不自禁
...and partly because well, they just keep coming to me.
但我得承认  丽莎一直都在夸你
But I have to admit that after all the wonderful things Lizzie has told me...
瑞秋又说了那么那么多故事
and the many, many, many stories that Rachel has told me...
看来
that, well
你也不是
you're not
那么坏
all bad.
"压根儿就不坏"
"Not all bad."
很抱歉之前对你那么苛刻   你得体谅我
And anyhow, I'm sorry I was so harsh before, But you have to understand.
丽莎在我眼里还是个12岁的小女孩
I still look at Lizzie like she's a 12-year-old girl.
我懂  我也有同感
You know, I know what you mean. I do that, too.
你说什么  不  我不是把她当成12岁小女孩
I beg your pardon? No! No! Not—I don't mean I-I see her as a 12-year-old girl.
我是说  我有个6岁大的儿子  在我眼里就还当是个小婴儿
I mean, I have a son who's, um, 6, and I still think of him as a baby.
你有儿子  对   我和前妻
You have a son? Yeah. My ex-wife and I...
共有孩子的监护权
...uh, share custody of Ben. And, uh--
还有  卡萝和我早已达成共识
Just so you know, Carol and I are on excellent terms...
相信你和你太太也是
...as I'm sure you are with your wife.
抱歉
Oh! I'm sorry.
真是的
It's unbelievable!
没事   我只是没意识到你结过婚
Don't worry about it, I just didn't realize you were married.
我们是结过婚   但那只是
Oh, we were. But that was just a...
只是酒后胡闹罢了
I mean, that was just a big drunken mistake.
你回来了
You're back.
你们俩结过婚了
You two were married?
抱歉  不好意思  你在讲艾蜜莉那次
Oh, whoops. I'm sorry. You were talking about Emily.
钱德   我们不是约好六点在咖啡馆碰头吗
Chandler, we said we would meet at the coffee house at 6:00.
约的是7点   约的6点
We said 7:00. We said 6:00!
我如果有提到6点
The only way that I said 6:00...
应该是说  "我们约7点   不要约6点"
...would be if I said the sentence, "Let's meet at 7:00, not at 6:00."
我如果有提到7点   应该会说
If I had said 7:00, maybe I would have said something like:
"我男朋友真是自作聪明  什么7点"
"Wow, my boyfriend is such a wiseass. 7:00!"
嗨  天哪
Hi! Oh my God!
我知道你们约几点  什么
I know what time you said. What?
我知道摩莎和钱特约的几点
Well, actually I know what time Chester and Marsha said.
几点  风水轮流转
What time? Quite an interesting turn of events.
我的书突然成了救星  对吧
Suddenly it's my book to the rescue, huh? Let's see.
有意思
Ooh. Very interesting.
这下  真相大白了
Yeah, well this certainly clears things up.
到底是几点   你们先
What does it say? I will tell you...
谢谢我写这本书   我就说
...as soon as you thank me for writing my book.
谢谢你写书  这真是一本好书
Thank you for writing your book. It's a great book...
你是女王中的女王
...and you are the queen of everything.
谢谢   你也是
Thanks. So are you.
我就说我不该穿这个颜色
I told you I should not wear this color.
"摩 摩莎和钱特  打算星期天晚上去看电影
"Monica-Marsha and Chester are planning on seeing a movie Sunday night.
摩莎觉得应该约6点
"Marsha thinks they're supposed to meet at 6:00.
而钱特觉得电影是7点"
Chester thinks it's at 7:00."
你知道我们会赶不上电影   没错
So you knew we would miss the movie? That's right.
你不警告我们   而只是把它写在这本白痴书里
Instead of telling us, you decided to write it in your stupid book?
"摩莎和钱特很生菲莉丝的气"
"Marsha and Chester are mad at Phyllis."
没想到我竟会失去这份工作
I can't believe I'm gonna lose this job.
真可惜   我能帮你什么忙吗
I'm so sorry, man. ls there anything I can do?
能  帮我把那个小冰箱搬走  不要被保安发现
Yeah. Help me get this mini-fridge past the security guard.
乔伊   我想和你谈谈
Hey, Joey, I want to talk to you.
是吗  我可不想理你  韦恩  我恨你  你毁了我的一生
Yeah? I don't want to talk to you, Wayne. I hate you. You ruined my life.
钱德  韦恩  韦恩  钱德  嗨  你好
Oh, Chandler, Wayne. Wayne, Chandler. Hi. How are you?
乔伊  如果你帮我  我就帮你拿回角色
Joey, I'll get you your job back if you help me out.
我为什么要帮你
Why should I help you out?
理由他已经说了  帮你什么
The reason he just said. What do you need?
我看到你跟那个美女搭讪
I saw you on stage talking to that beautiful woman.
你认得萨拉   我也想和她搭讪
You know, Sarah. I wish I could talk to her.
你爱上她了吗  对
Are you in love with her? Yeah.
所有的美女   谁都好
Her. All of them. Anyone.
我是过来人  我的朋友
Yeah. I've been there, my friend.
你教我怎样跟女人搭讪
Listen, I guarantee you keep your job...
我就保证让你留下来
...if you can teach me how to talk to women like you do.
韦恩  这种事怎么教法  不过是一种天生的本领
Oh, Wayne, it's not something you can teach y'know? It's pretty much something you're born with--
你能学得   我来教你
You can teach it. I can show you right now.
我是说   罗斯其实从每次婚姻中
I mean, if you think about it...
都学到了一点东西
...I mean Ross did learn something from each marriage.
学到如何让婚姻变短吗
How to make the next one even shorter? Oh.
等等   这么说不公平
Now wait a minute. That's not fair.
我们的婚姻比他和艾蜜莉的长
He was married to me a hell of a lot longer than he was to Emily.
他只是没告诉我
He just didn't tell me.
看样子我还得上趟洗手间
Maybe I have to pee again.
真有意思
Well, this is fun.
罗斯
So Ross...
有哪个老婆被你杀了吗
...did you kill any of these wives?
你知道吗
You know what? I--
我受够了  我很喜欢你的女儿
I have had enough of this. Y'know, I care a great deal about your daughter.
我一直很尊重她
And I have treated her with nothing but respect.
要是你对我有意见  说实话  你在对我吼叫吗
So if you've got a problem with me. frankly... Are you yelling at me'?
天啊  绝对没有
God, no.
你知道吗  爸  如果你不喜欢罗斯  也无所谓
You know what, Daddy? If you don't like Ross, that's fine.
我才不管   我还是要跟他交往
It doesn't matter to me. I'm gonna go outwith him anyway.
真的
Really?
要是她不管
Well, if it doesn't matter to her...
那我也不管   我没有吼叫
...it doesn't matter to me. Still not yelling.
我还能说什么呢
Well, what can I say?
我对你仍然没什么好感
This doesn't make me like you better.
这没什么  我对自己也不是很满意
That's okay. I'm not so crazy about myself right now either.
那我们达成共识  对  可以这么说
Then we agree? Yeah, I guess so.
我们没有人喜欢罗斯   我喜欢罗斯
Neither of us like Ross. I like Ross.
哦  你还小
Oh, heh, kids!
等等  我又想到罗斯人很好的故事了
Wait. I just thought of another story about how nice Ross is.
没关系  瑞秋  我们现在不喜欢罗斯了
That's okay, Rach. We're not liking Ross right now.
这种故事倒是很多
Oh! Well, I got a lot of those, too. Uh
结果你是对的  吉事
Well, it turns out you were right, C.H.E.E.S.E.
那批货根本没抵达奥马哈   没错
That shipment never made it to Omaha? You got it.
而且那个拉比的胡子  100%是马毛
And the rabbi's beard? 100 percent horse hair.
干得好   吉事
Nice catch, C.H.E.E.S.E.
吉事   该你说话了
It's your line, C.H.E.E.S.E.
韦恩  韦恩
Wayne! Wayne!